Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications, Part 1
6007
U.S. Department of Labor
27 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
27 cubic feet
United States.; United States. Dept. of Labor--Archives; United States. Dept. of Labor. Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation --Archives
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
- AAA Labor Management Committee - An Outline of Labour Adjustment. (Box 1)
  - Labor-Management Cooperation and Worker Participation: Elements of Program Development, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    December 1984
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Cooperation and Worker Participation: Elements of Program Development, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Author: Labor-Management Committee
      Format: Publication
      Language: English.
  - Aage, Hans. "Some Basic Issues in Economic Democracy", Economic and Industrial Democracy., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Volume 4, Number 1, February 1983, pp. 69-84.
    - Item 1: Some Basic Issues in Economic Democracy, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Author: Hans Aage
      Notes: Economic and Industrial Democracy, Vol. 4, No. 1
  - Abbott, Jan and Rose, Warren. "Turning Management Groups into Management Teams", Journal for Quality and Participation., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    December 1991, pp. 70-72.
    - Item 1: Turning Management Groups into Management Teams, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Author: Jan Abbot and Rose Warren
  - Abo, Tetsuo. "New Technology and Manpower Utilization in Japanese Automobile Firms in Japan and in their Plants in the US"., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Presented to The Seoul Workshop: Current Trends and Prospects of the World Auto Industry. Seoul, South Korea. May 18 - 19 1989.
    - Item 1: New Technology and Manpower Utilization in Japanese Automobile Firms in Japan and Their Plants in the United States, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Author: Tetsuo Abo
      Notes: Manuscript
  - Abowd, John M and Lemieux, Thomas. The Effects of International Competition on Collective Bargaining Outcomes: A Comparison of the United States and Canada., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Working Paper No. 3352, National Bureau of Economic Research, Washington, DC: May 1990.
    - Item 1: The Effects of International Competition on Collective Bargaining Outcomes: A Comparison of the United States and Canada, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Author: John M. Abowd and Thomas Lemieux
      Notes: Working Paper Series, Contains Graphs and Tables
  - Abowd, John; Farber, Henry S. Product Market Competition, Union Organizing Activity and Resistance., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Working Paper No. 3353, National Bureau of Economic Research, Washington, DC: May 1990.
    - Item 1: Product Market Competition, Union Organizing Activity, and Employer Resistance, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Author: John M. Abowd and Henry S. Farber
      Notes: Working Paper Series
  - Abramson, Mark A and Scanlon, John W. "The Five Dimensions". Government Executive., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    July 1991. pp. 20-25.
    - Item 1: The Five Dimensions: Organizations Cannot Depend Only on 'Star' Leadership, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Author: Mark A. Abramson and John W. Scanlon
  - Adachi, Christina January. "Profile: Secretary Lynn Martin". Today's Chicago Woman., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    November 1991. pp. 24-26.
    - Item 1: Profile: Secretary of Labor Lynn Martin, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Author: Adachi, Christine
      Notes: Article and Interview
  - Adams, J Stacy. "Wage Inequities, Productivity, and Work Quality". Industrial Relations -- A Journal of Economics and Society., 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Volume 3, Number 1, October 1963, pp. 9-16.
    - Item 1: Wage Inequities, Productivity and Work Quality, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Author: J. Stacy Adams
  - Addison, John T. "Trade Unions, Corporatism, and Inflation". Journal of Labor Research., 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Volume 5, Number 1, Winter 1984, pp. 39-62.
    - Item 1: Trade Unions, Corporatism, and Inflation, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Author: John T. Addison
  - The Changing Situations of Workers and their Unions. The AFL-CIO Committee on the Evolution of Work., 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Washington, DC. February 1985.
    - Item 1: The Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Author: Committee on the Evolution of Work
    - Item 2: The Changing Situation of Workers and Their Unions, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Explore Both Sides: US-Mexico Free Trade Agreement". AFL-CIO., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    February 1991.
    - Item 1: Exploiting Both Sides: U.S.-Mexico Free Trade, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Author: AFL-CIO
  - The Permanent Replacement of Workers Striking over Healthcare Benefits in 1990. AFL-CIO, Department of Employee Benefits., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Washington, DC. June 1991.
    - Item 1: The Permanent Replacement of Workers Striking Over Health Care Benefits in 1990, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Author: Department of Employee Benefits
  - "Reinvigorating the Public Service: Union Innovations to Improve Government". AFL-CIO Employee Department., 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    March 1992.
    - Item 1: Reinvigorating the Public Service: Union Innovations to Improve Government, 1992; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Author: Public Employee Department
  - The Pocketbook Issues: AFL-CIO Policy Recommendations for 1992. AFL-CIO., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Washington, DC. November 1991.
    - Item 1: The Pocketbook Issues: AFL-CIO Policy Recommendations for 1992, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Author: AFL-CIO: Executive Council
  - Facing the Future: AFSCME's Approach to Technology. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Washington, DC. May 1983.
    - Item 1: Facing the Future: AFSCME's Approach to Technology, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Author: AFSCME
  - Aaron, Benjamin and Harry T Edwards. The First Annual Benjamin Aaron Lecture on the Role of Public Policy in the Employment Relationship with Commentary., 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    UCLA Institute for Industrial Relations, Los Angeles, CA, October 1986.
    - Item 1: The First Annual Benjamin Aaron Lecture on the Role of Public Policy in the Employment Relationship, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Notes: Includes Commentary by Harry T. Edwards
  - Abbot, Jan. "New Approaches to Collective Bargaining and Workplace Relations Do They Work?". Ross Consulting Group., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Manuscript. Fremont, CA.
    - Item 1: New Approaches to Collective Bargaining and Workplace Relations: Do They Work?, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Author: Jan Abbott
      Notes: Preview publication
  - Abel, IW. Employment Security and Plant Productivity Committees in the Steel Industry. National Center for Productivity and Quality of Work life., 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Government Printing Office, Washington, DC. December 1974.
    - Item 1: Employment Security and Plant Productivity Committees: Ten Coordinating Steel Companies, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Author: I.W. Abel
  - Abernathy, William K, Kim B Clark and Alan M Kantrow. "The New Industrial Competition". Harvard Business Review., 1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    September - October 1981. pp. 68-79.
    - Item 1: The New Industrial Competition, 1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Author: William J. Abernathy, Kim B. Clark, and Alan M. Kantrow
  - Abo, Tetsuo (editor). "Local Production of Japanese Automobile and Electronic Firms in the US". Japanese Multinational Enterprise Study Group., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Local Production of Japanese Automobile Electronics Firms in the United States: The 'Application' and 'Adaptation' of Japanese Style Management, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Abo, Tetsuo. "The Application of Japanese-Style Management Concepts in Japanese Auto Plants in the US". The Future of the World Automobile Industry., 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Scince Center, Berlin, pp. 327-340.
    - Item 1: The Application of Japanese Style Management Concepts in Japanese Automobile Plants in the United States, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Abo, Tetsuo. "The Emergence of Japanese Multinational Enterprises and the Theory of Foreign Direct Investment"., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Japanese and European Management: Their International Adaptability. University of Tokyo Press, Tokyo, Japan. Pp. 3-17.
    - Item 1: The Emergence of Japanese Multinational Enterprises and the Theory of Foreign Direct Investment, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ackoff, Russell L and William B Deane. "The Revitalization of ALCOA's Tennessee Operations". National Productivity Review., 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Summer 1984. pp. 239-245.
    - Item 1: The Revitalization of ALCOA's Tennessee Operations, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Author: Russell L. Ackoff and William B. Deane
  - Acosta, Dan. "The People Movement". The Detroiter., 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
    May 1982. pp. 37-41.
    - Item 1: The People Movement, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Author: Dan Acosta
    - Item 2: The People Movement, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Role of Business in Education Reform: Blueprint for Action. Ad Hoc Committee on Education., 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
    The Business Roundtable, New York, New York.
    - Item 1: The Role of Business in Education: Blueprint for Action, 1988; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Author: Ad Hoc Committee on Education
  - Addison, John T and Pedro Portugal. "Prenotification of Impending Job Loss: From Voluntary Exchange to Mandated Benefits"., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
    The Symposium on the Future Roles of Unions, Industry, and Government in Industrial Relations. University of Minnesota. April 1990.
    - Item 1: Prenotification of Impending Job Loss: From Voluntary Exchange to Mandated Benefits, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Author: John T. Addison and Pedro Portugal
  - Adelmean, Nancy E. International Seminar on the Effects of Structural Change on Employment and Education in the Service Sector: A Summary., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Bureau of International Labor Affairs, US Department of Labor, Washington, DC. August 1989.
    - Item 1: International Seminar on the Effects of Structural Change on Employment and Education and Training in the Service Sector, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Author: Nancy E. Adelman
  - Addison, John T. "Are Unions Good for Productivity?". Journal of Labor Research., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Volume 3, Number 2. Spring 1983. pp. 125-138.
    - Item 1: Are Unions Good for Productivity?, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Addison, John T and Pedro Portugal. "The Effect of Advance Notification of Plant Closings on Unemployment". Industrial and Labor Relations Review., 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Volume 41, Number 1. October 1987. pp. 3-16.
    - Item 1: The Effect of Advance Notification of Plant Closings on Unemployment, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Author: John. Addison and Pedro Portugal
  - Adkins, Lynn. "A Formula for Labor Peace". Dun's Review., 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
    December 1978. pp 80,82.
    - Item 1: A Formula for Labor Peace, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Author: Lynn Adkins
  - Adkins, Lynn. "New State Strategies to Create Jobs". Dun's Business Month., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
    November 1983. pp. 64-65,69.
    - Item 1: New State Strategy to Create Jobs, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Adler, Paul S. "Capitalizing on New Manufacturing Technologies: Current Problems and Emergent Trends in US Industry"., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
    People and Technology in the Workplace, National Academy Press, Washington, DC. Pp. 59-88.
    - Item 1: Capitalizing on New Manufacturing Technologies: Current Problems and Emergent Trends in U.S. Industry, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Author: Paul S. Adler
  - Adler, Paul S and Robert Howard. "Technology and the Future of Work". Highlights of the Seminar Held at Stanford University., 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
    March 28 and 29, 1990.
    - Item 1: Technology and the Future of Work: Highlights of the Seminar held at Stanford University, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Author: Paul S. Adler and Robert Howard
  - Adler, Paul S. The Productivity Puzzle: Number Alone Won't Solve It". Monthly Labor Review., 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
    October 1982. pp. 15-21.
    - Item 1: The Productivity Puzzle: Numbers Alone Won't Solve It, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Adler, Paul S. "When Knowledge is the Critical Resource, Knowledge Management is the Critical Task"., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    IEE Transactions on Engineering Management. Volume 36, Number 2. May 1989. pp. 87-94.
    - Item 1: When Knowledge is the Critical Resources, Knowledge Management is the Critical Task, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Adolf, Barbara and Karol Rose. "Child Care: Perceiving the Need, Delivering the Options". Personnel Journal., 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Volume 65, Number 6. June 1986. pp. 57-65.
    - Item 1: Perceiving the Need, Delivering the Options, 1986; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
      Author: Barbara Adolf and Karol Rose
  - "Advantages and Limitations of Current Employee Ownership Assistance Acts to Workers Facing a Plant Closure". The Hastings Law Journal., 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Volume 36. September 1984. pp. 93=120.
    - Item 1: Advantages and Limitations of Current Employee Ownership Assistance Acts to Workers Facing a Plant Closure, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Author: Virginia L. Duquet
  - Europe 1992. Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiations., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Washington, DC. November 1989.
    - Item 1: Europe 1992: Report of the Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiatoins, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Author: Advisory Committee for Trade Policy and Negotiations
  - Afzelius, Diane. "Twenty-Five Women Employees in the State Sector Speak Out on Sex Equality: A Summary". Economic and Industrial Democracy., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Volume 4, Number 1. February 1983. pp. 117-119.
    - Item 1: Twenty-Five Women Employees in the State Sector Speak Out on Sexual Equality: A Summary, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Author: Diane Afzelius
  - Agnew, Bill. "Quality Circles: An Expression of Change at the Grass Roots". Industrial and Commercial Training., 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Volume 14, Number 3. March 1982. pp. 86-88.
    - Item 1: Quality Circles: An Expression of Change at the Grass Roots, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Author: Bill Agnew
  - Agee, Lynn. "Some Union, Employee and Employer Rights Under the Reagan National Labor Review Board: Done with Dotson"., 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
    The Fifth Annual Multi-State Labor and Employment Law Seminar. Atlanta, Georgia. April 2-3 1987.
    - Item 1: Some Union, Employee and Employer Rights Under the Reagan NLRB: Done with Dotson?, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Author: Lynn Agee
  - Aguren, Stefan. An Example of Decentralization from Volvo, Olofstromsverkin. Management Media., 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Stockholm, 1982.
    - Item 1: Companies within companies: An Example of Decentralization from Volvo, Olofstromsverken, 1982; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
      Author: Stefan Aguren
  - Aguren, Stefan. "From Industrial Relations to Learning Organizations". The Swedish Management Group., Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Stockholm, Sweden.
    - Item 1: From Industrial Relations to Learning Organizations: The organization of work in a dynamic business and social environment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Aguren, Stefan, Reine Hansson and KG Karlsson. The Volvo Kalmar Plant: The Impact of New Design on Work Organization., 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    The Rationalization Council, SAF-LO. Stockholm, Sweden. September 1976.
    - Item 1: The Volvo Kalmar Plant: The Impact of new Design on Work Organization, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
      Author: Stefan Aguren, Reine Hansson, and K.G. Karlsson
  - Ahern, Robert W. The Labor-Management Committee: An Organizational Change Process. Buffalo-Erie County Labor-Management Council., 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Buffalo, NY. November 1985.
    - Item 1: The Labor Management Committee: An Organizational Change Process, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Author: Robert W. Ahern
  - Ahern, Robert W. "The Collective Bargaining Process and Organization Development". Buffalo-Erie County Labor-Management Council., 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    September 1979.
    - Item 1: The Collective Bargaining Process and Organization Development, 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
      Notes: manuscript
    - Item 2: The Collective Bargaining Process and Organization Development, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Ahern, Robert W. Positive Labor Relations Plant Labor Management Committees and the Collective Bargaining Process"., 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Buffalo-Eire County Labor-Management Council. Buffalo, New York. April 1978.
    - Item 1: Sympsium on Labor-Management Committees: State of the Art, 1980; Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
      Author: Robert W. Ahern and William L. Holcomb
      Notes: See Steve Donahue for Check-Out Procedures
  - Ahlburg, Dennis A and James B Dworkin. "The Influence of Macroeconomic Variables on the Probability of Union Decertification"., 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Journal of Labor Research. Volume 5, Number 1. Winter 1984. pp. 13-28.
    - Item 1: Positive Labor Relations Plant Labor Management Committees and the Collective Bargaining Process, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Ainsworth, Robert G. An Overview of the Labor Market Problems of Indians and Native Americans. National Commission for Employment Policy., 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Washington, DC. January 1989. Report No. 89002.
    - Item 1: The Influence of Macroeconomic Variables on the Probability of Union Decertification, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
      Author: Dennis A. Ahlburg and James B. Dworkin
  - Alban, Billie T. "Training Every Employee as a Business Person". Manuscript., Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Undated.
    - Item 1: An Overview of the Labor Market Problems of Indian and Native Americans, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
      Author: Robert G. Ainsworth
    - Item 2: An Overview of the Labor Market Problems of Indian and Native Americans, 1989; Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Albin, Peter S. "Job Design, Control Technology and Technological Change". Journal of Economic Issues., 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Volume 19, Number 3. September 1985. pp. 703-730.
    - Item 1: Training Every Employee and a Business Person, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
      Author: Billie T. Alban
  - Albin, Peter S. "Who Should Design Jobs". Adherent., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Volume 10, Number 2. Fall 1983. pp. 48-55.
    - Item 1: Job Design, Control Technology, and Technical Change, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
      Author: Peter S. Albin
  - Alderfer, Clayton O. "Job Enlargement and the Organizational Context". Personnel Psychology., 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Volume 2. pp. 418-426.
    - Item 1: Who Should Design Jobs?, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Alexander, C Philip. "Learning from the Japanese". Personnel Journal., 1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
    August 1981. pp. 616-619.
    - Item 1: Job Engagement and the Organizational Context, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
      Author: Clayton P. Alderfer
  - Alexander, Kenneth O, Daniel Yankelovich and John Immerwahr. "The Changing American Workplace". Technology Review., 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Volume 86, Number 6. November-December 1983. pp. 12-17.
    - Item 1: Learning from the Japanese, 1981; Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
      Author: C. Philip Alexander
  - Alexander, Kenneth O. "On Work and Authority: Issues in Job Enlargement, Job Enrichment, Worker Participation and Shared Authority". American Journal of Economics and Sociology., 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Volume 34, Number 1. January 1975. pp. 43-54.
    - Item 1: The Changing American Workplace, 1983; Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
      Author: Kenneth O. Alexander, Daniel Yankelovich, and John Immerwahr
  - Alexander, Kenneth O. "The Promise and Perils of Worker Participation in Management". American Journal of Economics and Sociology., 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Volume 43. Number 2. April 1984. pp. 197-204.
    - Item 1: On Work and Authority: Issues in Job Enlargement, Job Enrichment, Worker Participation and Shared Authority, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
      Author: Kenneth O. Alexander
  - Allair, Paul A. "Quality: Where it Has Been and Where it is Going". Journal for Quality and Participation., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
    March 1991. pp. 64-66.
    - Item 1: The Promise and Perils of Worker Participation in Management, 1984; Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Allaire, Paul A, Rickard, Norman E. "Quality and Participation at Xerox". Journal for Quality and Participation., Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Volume 12, Number 1. pp. 24-26.
    - Item 1: Quality: Where it Has Been and Where it is Going, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
      Author: Paul A. Allaire
  - Allen, John H. "Making Lifetime Employment a US Reality: The Toyota Experience". Employment Relations Today., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Summer 1991. pp. 185-192.
    - Item 1: Quality and Participation at Xerox, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
      Author: Paul A. Allaire and Norman E. Rickard
  - Allen, Linda G. "Quality: The Decimal Point Moves Over". Automation., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    March 1991. pp. 36-40.
    - Item 1: Making Lifetime Employment a U.S. Reality: The Toyota Experience, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
      Author: John H. Allen
  - Allen, Mary. "Benefits, Buffet Style". Nation's Business., 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Volume 75, Number 1. January 1987. pp. 45-47.
    - Item 1: Quality: The Decimal Point Moves Over, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
      Author: Linda G. Allen
  - Allen, Russell. "Symposium: The Professional in Unions and His Educational Preparation". Industrial and Labor Relations Review., 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Volume 16, Number 1. October 1962. pp. 16-29.
    - Item 1: Benefits, Buffet Style, 1987; Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)